<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supreme Recipes</title>
    <link>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Supreme Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hearty Oatmeal</title>
      <link>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/hearty-breakfast-oatmeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/hearty-breakfast-oatmeal/</guid>
      <description>If your Oatmeal isn’t Hearty Breakfast Oatmeal… Is it even Oatmeal?
⏲️ Prep time: 5 min 🍳Cook time: 10 min 🍽️ Serving: 1 hearty serving Ingredients 1/2 cup Large Flake Oats (no partially cooked quick-oats allowed!) Almonds Pecans 1 Tbsp Roasted Flax Seed 1 Tbsp Hemp Hearts Cranberries (adjust amount to preference) 1/2 Banana (mashed) 1 cup Milk (3.25% if possible) Cinnamon (adjust amount to preference) 1 Egg ON Vanilla Ice Cream Protein Powder (optional) Directions Chop or mash nuts and fruit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meatloaf</title>
      <link>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/meatloaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/meatloaf/</guid>
      <description>This recipe will result in two or three glass dishes of tasty, moist meatloaf. Great for family suppers.
preptime: 30 min cooktime: 1 hour 10 minutes servings: 6+Once thawed, put all of your beef into a bowl. The next 4 steps will all go into this same bowl. Ingredients 4 ½ pounds Ground beef 1 Onion 2 Slices of bread 4 Eggs ¼ Cup of milk Garlic salt Onion powder Mustard Sugar free ketchup 3 Cubes of brown sugar 1 Can of Campbell’s tomato soup Franks RedHot sauce (Optional) Directions Dice the onion and bread slices into small pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Beef Soup</title>
      <link>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/medieval-beef-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/medieval-beef-soup/</guid>
      <description>Medieval beef soup with turnips and turnip greens.
Ingredients One beef roast Around three to four large turnips with their greens attached Two cups of chicken stock 1/10 grams of Saffron 1/4 a stick of butter A slow cooker A bowl of warm water. Directions Cube the roast into bite sized pieces and place them in a large skillet with the butter. Heat the pan on medium-high heat and brown the meat with the melted butter until the outside is evenly cooked, sprinkle with pepper as it browns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noodle Soup</title>
      <link>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/japanese-noodle-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/japanese-noodle-soup/</guid>
      <description>This is a very easy and simple Japanese style ramen noodle soup. This is very cheap to make, and you can really customise this however you wish with the garnish. This is my own spin inspired by other recipes that I found.
preptime: 20 min cooktime: 20 minutes servings: 4 Ingredients 750ml Chicken stock 4 Pork chops OR 4 Chicken Breasts Set honey 3 Garlic cloves Soy sauce Worcestershire sauce Ginger, sliced Chinese 5 Spice 1 Red Chilli, sliced and deseeded (Optional, but recommended) 375g Ramen Noodles (Medium Egg Noodles work well too) 100g Spinach (Optional) 4 Tbsp Sweetcorn (Optional) Sesame seeds (Optional) 4 Boiled Eggs (Optional) 1 Sheet of Dried Nori (Optional) Spring Onion, chopped (Optional) Directions For the broth, add 700ml of chicken stock to a large boiling pot with the garlic, ginger, soy sauce, chinese five spice, chili, and 300ml of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein Oat Cake</title>
      <link>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/oat-and-protein-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/oat-and-protein-cake/</guid>
      <description>Macros Calories: 464 Protein: 44g Carbs: 56g Fat: 7g Ingredients 60g oats 1 egg 1/2 tsp of baking powder 1/2 tsp of vanilla extract 100ml of almond milk or milk of choice 1 banana 1 cup of whey protein Instructions Blend the oats to make flour. Add the egg, baking powder, vanilla extract, milk and banana. Blend. Add one cup of whey protein. Blend again. Add to a greased baking dish and microwave for 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spanish Tortilla</title>
      <link>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/spanish-tortilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maksurtm.github.io/supreme-recipes/spanish-tortilla/</guid>
      <description>Things like the slicing of the potato, the amount of salt and how curdled is the inner part of the tortilla depend on your own taste. Don’t be afraid to experiment!
preptime: 5 min cooktime: 35 minutes servings: 6 Ingredients 8 free-range eggs 1 kg of potatoes 1 white onion Extra virgin olive oil Directions Peel, rinse and dry the potatoes. Cut the potatoes into thin slices. Put in a bowl, add salt to taste and stir.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
